So far in this lesson we've talked about phrases we can use to express different levels of certainty
到目前为止，在本课中，我们已经讨论了可以用来表达不同程度确定性的短语
about the future.
关于未来。
We've talked about how we can ask questions about the future.
我们已经讨论了如何提出有关未来的问题。
EXPRESS hypotheticals.
表达假设。
Talk about our intentions and how we can explain different possibilities alternatives for the future
谈论我们的意图以及我们如何解释未来的不同可能性替代方案
whether or not something happens.
不管有没有发生。
Now we need to actually put it together in a real life situation in a job interview.
现在我们需要在求职面试中将其实际放在现实生活中。
So let's imagine you're applying for a job in a big company and the job is related to finance finances.
因此，让我们假设您正在申请一家大公司的工作，并且该工作与财务有关。
Money related stuff and you're at the job interview you're sitting there.
与金钱有关的东西，而你在面试时就坐在那里。
The other person maybe from H.R. is sitting across from you.
另一个可能来自人力资源部的人坐在你对面。
They ask you a really common question.
他们问你一个非常常见的问题。
The question is So where do you see yourself in five years.
问题是，五年后你会在哪里看到自己。
And how will you get there.
你将如何到达那里。
What that means is what do you imagine you'll be like in five years.
这意味着你想象五年后你会是什么样子。
What do you imagine you'll be doing in terms of your career and maybe also your life.
你认为你会在你的职业生涯甚至你的生活方面做什么。
And how will you get there.
你将如何到达那里。
That means what actions do you need to take in order to achieve that idea that you have about yourself
这意味着你需要采取什么行动来实现你对自己的想法
in five years.
五年内。
You need to be able to clearly express your ideas about the future in this sort of answer.
您需要能够在此类答案中清楚地表达您对未来的想法。
So let's practice an example.
所以让我们练习一个例子。
I think it's really likely that I'll be working in a management capacity management capacity.
我认为我很可能会从事管理能力管理工作。
Here just means some role.
这里只是意味着一些角色。
Related to management or managing people.
与管理或管理人员有关。
A management role you could also say that some management capacity at some firm related to my field
一个管理角色，你也可以说在一些与我的领域相关的公司的一些管理能力
of finance.
的金融。
Be careful not to use major majors only when you're in school.
注意不要只在上学时使用专业。
Once you leave school you have a field.
一旦你离开学校，你就有了一个领域。
What's your field architecture finance accounting.
你的领域架构财务会计是什么。
Maybe you're doing something in arts.
也许你正在做一些艺术方面的事情。
Maybe you're a designer.
也许你是一名设计师。
Maybe your field is manufacturing.
也许你的领域是制造业。
If I'm hired here I will work toward that goal.
如果我被录用在这里，我会朝着这个目标努力。
So we have a very clear expression of the future.
所以我们对未来有一个非常清晰的表达。
I will work toward that goal very certain very confident.
我会非常肯定非常有信心地朝着这个目标努力。
And I think it would be a win win a win win means you get a benefit and I get a benefit.
我认为这将是一场胜利胜利胜利意味着你得到好处，我得到好处。
I think it would be a win win because my attention to detail and knack for picking up new skills makes
我认为这将是双赢，因为我对细节的关注和掌握新技能的诀窍使
me I think an asset.
我认为是一种资产。
So a knack for something means you have a natural skill for that a natural ability to do that.
因此，对某事的诀窍意味着您具有天生的技能，天生就有这样做的能力。
A knack for maybe understanding how people feel.
可能了解人们的感受的诀窍。
Learning languages.
学习语言。
This person is saying I will do this.
这个人说我会这样做。
This is my next action.
这是我的下一步行动。
I'm very certain about it.
我对此非常肯定。
And then an expression about the future.
然后是关于未来的表达。
That's a little less certain but still pretty clear and expressing a desire.
这有点不太确定，但仍然很清楚并表达了一种愿望。
I think it would be a win win.
我认为这将是一场双赢。
It would be a win win.
这将是一场双赢。
I'm hoping I'm hoping I'm hoping.
我希望我希望我希望。
I hope it's the same thing that I can move to an upper management position although I obviously have
我希望这与我能升任高层管理职位是一样的，尽管我显然有
a lot to learn using hope here means that you really don't know but that's your desire.
在这里使用希望来学习很多东西意味着你真的不知道，但那是你的愿望。
Remember it's completely uncertain what will happen but you can say you hope to express a desire.
请记住，完全不确定会发生什么，但您可以说您希望表达一种愿望。
If I do that means if I get a high level position an upper management position if I do means we're talking
如果我这样做意味着如果我获得高级职位如果我这样做意味着我们正在谈论高级管理职位
about possibilities alternatives.
关于可能性的替代品。
If I do I may work on getting an MBA.
如果我这样做，我可能会努力获得 MBA 学位。
If we want to be more certain here we could say if I do I will work on getting an MBA.
如果我们想在这里更加确定，我们可以说如果我这样做，我将努力获得 MBA。
An MBA is an advanced degree related to business and often people will get an MBA as they continue their
MBA 是与商业相关的高级学位，人们通常会在继续学习时获得 MBA
career so they don't just quit their job and work on the MBA.
这样他们就不会只是辞掉工作去攻读 MBA。
They may do them at the same time so that they can constantly increase their skill level and their knowledge
他们可以同时做，这样他们就可以不断提高他们的技能水平和知识
regardless regardless means if it happens or not if it happens or not.
不管发生与否意味着它是否发生。
That means if I get my MBA or not regardless I'm going to constantly work to expand my knowledge of
这意味着无论我是否获得MBA学位，我都会不断努力扩展我的知识
the field and continue working on my English skills span means gets bigger.
该领域并继续努力提高我的英语技能跨度意味着变得更大。
Expand my knowledge of the field finances the field and continue working on my English skills as I realize
扩展我对该领域的知识为该领域提供资金，并在我意识到时继续提高我的英语技能
my accent can sometimes be an issue for people.
我的口音有时会成为人们的问题。
So if English is your second language and you speak English often at work but maybe you have a heavy
因此，如果英语是您的第二语言，并且您在工作中经常说英语，但也许您的负担很重
accent Your pronunciation is not so clear.
口音 你的发音不是很清楚。
You can say that you're aware of that and then use that to express a desire to improve to acknowledge
你可以说你意识到这一点，然后用它来表达想要改进的愿望
that yes.
是的。
I realize this is something that's not perfect but I am working on it.
我意识到这并不完美，但我正在努力。
So if you say as I realize my accent can sometimes be an issue for people that doesn't mean that people
所以如果你说我意识到我的口音有时会成为人们的问题，但这并不意味着人们
don't like me because of my accent It means that maybe some time my accent can be a little bit heavy
因为我的口音不喜欢我 这意味着也许有一段时间我的口音会有点重
or thick THC okay and that might make it a little difficult for people to understand.
或厚 THC 可以，这可能会让人们有点难以理解。
Sometimes if you have a thick or heavy accent.
有时，如果您的口音很重或很重。
I'm hoping this role will be the next big step in my career.
我希望这个角色将是我职业生涯的下一个重要步骤。
Again just expressing a desire and it's good to say I hope I hope if sometimes you don't have a lot
再次只是表达一个愿望，说我希望我希望如果有时你没有很多
of control over the situation.
对局势的控制。
They will decide if you get the job or not.
他们会决定你是否得到这份工作。
All you can do is talk about what you will do if good things happen.
你所能做的就是谈论如果有好事发生你会怎么做。
If you get the job and you can express your desire that this you feel is a good fit.
如果你得到这份工作，并且你可以表达你的愿望，你觉得这很合适。
This company is really where you want to be.
这家公司真的是你想去的地方。
OK so hopefully you can see how these phrases come together in a natural way in a real situation.
好的，希望您能在真实情况下看到这些短语如何以自然的方式组合在一起。
As usual we need to practice what we learn.
像往常一样，我们需要练习我们学到的东西。
So here is your assignment with all of the words and phrases and different sentence structures that
所以这是你的所有单词和短语以及不同的句子结构的作业
we practiced in this lesson.
我们在本课中进行了练习。
Put it together.
把它放在一起。
Talk about what your future goals are.
谈谈你未来的目标是什么。
Explain them in detail and then explain the things you can do in the near term to reach those goals.
详细解释它们，然后解释你在短期内可以做些什么来实现这些目标。
This is a good one because you have to talk about the near future which may be more certain more clear.
这是一个很好的选择，因为您必须谈论不久的将来，这可能会更确定更清楚。
I'm going to I will.
我要去我会的。
And talk about things that are farther in the future that you have less control over.
并谈论您无法控制的更远的未来。
I'd like to.
我想。
I hope and be sure to use some of the other expressions as well.
我希望并且一定要使用其他一些表达方式。
For example the alternatives using if to express what you might do if this happens or this happens.
例如，使用 if 来表达如果发生这种情况或发生这种情况你可能会做什么的替代方案。
OK try your best you can record yourself when you listen back to the recording.
好的，尽量你自己听录音的时候自己录。
Try to catch small mistakes write them down and then try it again.
试着抓住小错误，把它们写下来，然后再试一次。
In fact once you become more aware of your English speaking you can begin to pick out things that you
事实上，一旦你对自己的英语口语有了更多的了解，你就可以开始挑选你喜欢的东西
can improve.
可以改善。
Notice things that you can improve and over time get better.
注意你可以改进的事情，随着时间的推移会变得更好。
Even if you're not actually speaking with another person it is a good way to practice by yourself.
即使您实际上并没有与另一个人交谈，这也是您自己练习的好方法。
All right.
好的。
Good luck.
祝你好运。